MALTITI A. TAHIRU

Spanaway, WA 98387 • mtahiru@uw.edu • 404-863-7266

PROFILE STATEMENT

Interested in coding and learning to program. Intend to be Information Technology major for Fall, 2023. Over 2 years of fast-food experience providing exceptional customer service. Duties included communicating with customers in person and handling customer orders and questions over phone. Comfortable working in a fast-paced environment, adapting as needed and interacting with people of all ages .

Education

University of Washington-Tacoma

BS, Information Technology

Tacoma, WA June 2024

Experience

Amazon, Costco

Warehouse Worker

Sumner, WA

September 2021 – September 2022

- Assembled over 3,000 packages to be delivered to customers.
- Organized over 1,000 packages delivered to customers.
- Unload and load pallets from trucks.

AAFES

Food Worker

JBLM. WA

November 2018 – June 2021

- Answered store phone to take customer orders and answer questions daily.
 - Prepared and served thousands of meals to customers.
 - Communicated with customers to ensure all their needs were met.
 - Communicates effectively with coworkers to complete tasks
 - Guided new employees in learning skills needed on the job.

Leadership & Activities

Islamic Center of Tacoma

Volunteer

Tacoma WA

September 2018 - June 2021

- Assisted younger students in learning to read Arabic.
- Provided support to teachers in teaching students Islamic lessons.

Franklin Pierce Soccer Club

Volunteer

Tacoma WA September 2018 - November 2018

- Coached children in learning basic soccer skills.
- Explained
- Coordinated training sessions for practices.
- Assisted head-coach during games and practices.

Skills & Interests

Islamic Center of Tacoma

Volunteer

Tacoma WA September 2018 - June 2021

- Assisted younger students in learning to read Arabic.
- Provided support to teachers in teaching students Islamic lessons.

Programming: Java, HTML, CSS **Interests:** Web development, Soccer